Name: Shrijan Tiwari Address: 42 Thornleigh Road, Jesmond, Newcastle Upon Tyne, United Kingdom

Postal Code: NE2 3ET Mobile Number: +44 07436603316 Email: shrijansoftware39@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Recently completed Master of Science in Computer Game Engineering from Newcastle University. I have over 3 years of work experience as a Front End Developer/Software Developer. I have over 3 years of experience with technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue and Angular.

Link to my Portfolio – https://shrijan42.github.io/

## **Employment History**

September 2022 - Present

Front-End Software Developer - Motivait (Newcastle upon Tyne, United Kingdom)

- Working as a Front-End Software Developer using Javascript, AngularJS and Node.js in projects such as Zebra Island and Zebra Dashboard.
- Working as a Software Developer in projects such as FFDT, Newcastle Helix and BUS1016 using JavaScript, Angular 13, CMS and SASS.

October 2018-March 2020

Front End Developer/Software Developer - HiUp Solutions (Nepal/Head Office:Ireland)

- Develop and enhance frontend platform website/web application/API for Connected Portfolio-Premier-Education-Group and Apprenticeship.
- Design and develop new front end application for various platforms. Help out with front-end work on other application (HTML/CSS/Javascript/Vue/Angular in Node.js applications.)

# March 2018-August 2018

Front End Developer/Software Developer-Deerwalk Inc (Nepal/Head Office: U.S.A.)

- Design and develop new front end application for Plan Analytics and other big data solutions based on U.S. health care sector.
- Feature, Support, Bug and Report Task in Deerwalk's Plan Analytics application and Executive Analytics applications using Javascript, Bootstrap, Java and Angular.

January 2017-November 2017

Web Developer/Front End Developer -Deerwalk Group Ltd. (Nepal)

 Design and Develop web application for Deerwalk which includes Deerwalk CTEVT web application, Deerwalk Library Management System and Hospital Management System web application using HTML , CSS , Javascript , Angular , Bootstrap , Typescript and SASS.

## **Education**

Master of Science in Computer Game Engineering (2021-2022) - Newcastle University

#### **Grade – Distinction**

CSC8501 : Advanced Programming for Games

CSC8502 : Advanced Graphics for Games

CSC8503 : Advanced Game Technologies

o CSC8507 : Game Technology Innovations

o CSC8508 : Engineering Gaming Solutions within a Team

CSC8599: Project and Dissertation in Computer Game Engineering

Bachelor of Science (Hons) in Computing (2014-2017) (Date of Graduation: December 4 2017) - Islington College (London Metropolitan University)

## **Grade - Second Class Honours**

- FC6PO1NI Project
- CS6004NI Application Development
- o FC6W51NI Work Related Learning II
- o CU6051NI Artificial Intelligence
- CC1002NI Problem Solving For IT
- o CC1003NI Introduction to the Internet
- o CC1006NI Introduction to Programming
- CC1007NI Further Programming
- o CC1008NI Personal Development for Computing
- o CC1HO1NI Study Skills For Computing
- o CC2005NI Project Planning and Management
- CC2006NI Data Modelling and Database Systems
- CC2007NI Software Engineering I
- CC2008NI Object-Oriented Analysis and Design
- CC2009NI Communication Networks
- o CC2011NI Operating Systems
- o CC2018NI Professional Development For Computing
- o CC2E01NI Employment Skills For Computing
- o CT1044NI Computer Hardware and Software Architecture
- o MA1032NI Logic
- CC6001NI Advanced Database Systems and Development

## **Key Skills (Technical Skills)**

HTML	C++	OpenGL	Node.js
CSS	C#	Blender	<b>J</b>
JavaScript	Unity	Autodesk 3ds Max	
TypeScript	Unreal Engine	Adobe Photoshop	
Angular	Lua	LESS	
Bootstrap	Java	SASS	
Vue.js	React	jQuery	

# Languages

Nepali (Native or Fluent), English (Fluent), Hindi (Fluent), German (Beginner)